zcric.com 2015-04-20

# Privacy Policy - Cricket Highlights Online - Zcic.com | Cricket Highlights Online - Zcic.com

Keeping in mind the importance of privacy of personal information of visitors to this site, the following details the kinds of information that is collected as part of the process of serving Advertisements on this site, and how this information is safeguarded. By visiting Zcric.com, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers Zcric.com ’s treatment of personal information that Zcric.com gathers when you are on the Zcric.com website and when you use Zcric.com services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Zcric.com does not own or control, or to individuals that Zcric.com does not employ or manage.

**Information collected by Zcric.com:**  
Zcric.comonly collects personal information that is relevant to the purpose of the website. This information allows Zcric.com to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. Zcric.com does not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. Zcric.com collects the following types of information from its users:

**1.**  Information You provide through the comments section: The information provided is entirely up to you and you may choose not to provide certain information.

**2.**  Log Files:  
As is the norm with most websites, data located in log files is collected and used by Zcric.com and its authorized agents. The information in the log files includes a visitor’s IP address, ISP, browser used at the time of visit to the site, the time you visited and the distribution of pages navigated on this site. Zcric.com uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.  
Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Zcric.com will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if you cannot be recognized, Zcric.com wants you to be aware that these programs are available.

**3.  **E-mail Communications  
Zcric.com is very concerned about your privacy and will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. You will receive anemail from Zcric.com only if you have specifically subscribed to email reminders about new postings on the site.

**4.  **Cookies:  
Third party advertisements are made use of on this site to support maintenance of the site. The advertisers use technology including cookies as part of providing advertisements on this site, which send the third-party vendor anonymous non-personally identifiable information including your IP address, ISP, browser used at the time of visit to this site, and in some cases, info on whether you have Flash installed. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser that provide information which is used for geo-targeting purposes in order to display advertisements appropriate to your location and your browsing-patterns while visiting this site. Zcric.com cookies do not collect personal information, and Zcric.com

does not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to find out who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.  
You may choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies through the settings provided in your browser, or by controlling the preferences in programs like Norton Internet Security. However, this may affect some of your interaction with this site as well as other websites.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You can specifically opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting  **[this page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)**.

**Please Note** : Neither do these ad-serving technologies in any way hinder or cause you any problems while using the internet to visit this or other sites nor do they spy on you in any way to collect information other than those mentioned. Their sole purpose is to display ads most appropriate to you based on your location.

Minors Under 18 Years of Age  
It is recommend that minors ask and receive their parents’ permission before using Zcric.com or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

**Changes to this  Privacy Policy**  
Zcric.com may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information Zcric.com collects now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If Zcric.com makes changes to the Privacy Policy, you will be notified through an announcement on the website so you are always aware of what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

**Conditions of Use**  
If you decide to visit the Zcric.com website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to thisPrivacy Policy and Zcric.com ’s Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes.

**Effective Date of this  Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 19, 2010 and last updated February 16, 2011.
